module.exports = [{id: 1, category:"Sports",type:"multiple", question:"Who won the very 1st World Cup in 1930?",correct_answer:"Uruguay",incorrect_answers:["Argentina","Italy","Brazil"]},
{category:"Science",type:"multiple", question:"What is the correct term for a group of pandas?",correct_answer:"An 'embarrassment' of pandas",incorrect_answers:["A 'washing machine' of pandas","An 'envelope' of pandas","A 'suspicion' of pandas"]},{id: 2,category:"Music",type:"multiple",question:"What was blink-182's last studio album recorded with Scott Raynor as the drummer before he was replaced by Travis Barker?",correct_answer:"Dude Ranch",incorrect_answers:["Cheshire Cat","Buddha","Enema of the State"]},{id: 3,category:"Science",type:"multiple",question:"Here we have four hypothetical titles of journal articles. One of them is written by a fake scientist who is just making shit up that could never actually happen. Try to spot the fraudulent scientist.",correct_answer:"Phylogenetic relationships among algae and tunicates based on complete large-subunit rRNA sequences",incorrect_answers:["Novel sound production through contingency learning in Odobenus rosmarus (Walrus)","Assessing the consequences of the pesticide methoxychlor: neuroendocrine and behavioral measures as indicators of biological impact of an estrogenic environmental chemical","Cooperation among conspecifics following color-induced neophobia in the context of feeding present in Larus californicus"]},
{id: 4, category:"Science: Computers",type:"multiple",question:"Here we have four hypothetical titles of journal articles. One of them is written by a fake scientist who is just making shit up that could never actually happen. Try to spot the fraudulent scientist.",correct_answer:"Relationships between soaring conditions and use of a communal roost by Turkey Vultures in northeastern Iowa",incorrect_answers:["Sequencing of the zebra finch (Taeniopygia guttata) and assessment of number of interchromosomal rearrangements between it and the wild turkey (Meleagris gallopavo)", "Changes in turkey eggshell permeability in strains selected for increased egg production or growth","Isolation and characterization of mitochondria from turkey spermatozoa using a discontinuous Percoll gradient"]},
{id: 5, category:"Science",type:"multiple",question:"Here we have four hypothetical titles of journal articles. One of them is written by a fake scientist who is just making shit up that could never actually happen. Try to spot the fraudulent scientist.",correct_answer:"Simultaneous tetragyny in Northern Lapwing (Vanellus vanellus)",incorrect_answers:["Reproductive success and nestling diet in the Lesser Spotted Great Tit (Heptanoides minor)","The evolution of high summit metabolism and cold tolerance in birds and its impact on present‐day distributions","Patterns of mitochondrial DNA and alloenzyme evolution in Ammodramus"]},{id: 6,category:"Science",type:"multiple",question:"Here we have four hypothetical titles of journal articles. One of them is written by a fake scientist who is just making shit up that could never actually happen. Try to spot the fraudulent scientist.",correct_answer:"Chapeau",incorrect_answers:["Bonnet"," &Eacute;charpe"," Casque"]},{id: 7,category:"Entertainment: Music",type:"multiple",question:"Here we have four hypothetical titles of journal articles. One of them is written by a fake scientist who is just making shit up that could never actually happen. Try to spot the fraudulent scientist.",correct_answer:"Subadult plumage in North American finches and tests of models for the evolution of delayed plumage maturation",incorrect_answers:["Evolution of sex‐biased maternal effects in birds: sex‐specific resource allocation among simultaneously growing oocytes","Competition, predation and nest niche shifts among convergent canopy nesters: phylogeny and natural history evolution of parrots (Psittaciformes) and trogons (Trogoniformes)","Independent evolution of migration over the Central and South American landscape in a long‐distance temperate tropical migratory bird (Myiarchus swainsoni)"]},{id: 8,category:"Science",type:"multiple",question:"Here we have four hypothetical titles of journal articles. One of them is written by a fake scientist who is just making shit up that could never actually happen. Try to spot the fraudulent scientist.",correct_answer:"Fine scale topographical influences on environmental potential for polygamy and male reproductive success in the greater yellowlegs (T. melanoleuca)",incorrect_answers:["Male-male competition and infanticide among chimpanzees (P. troglodytes)","Effects of female polyandry coevolving with increased hatching rate in birds on infertility in the northern jacana (J. spinosa)","The evolution of punishment in n-player public goods games: a volunteer’s dilemma"]},{id: 9,category:"Television", type:"multiple",question:"What is the name of the currency that Stealy uses to measure tha value of the common office items he stole during his stealing spree featured on the Interdimensional Cable II episode of Rick and Morty?",correct_answer:"Grapples",incorrect_answers:["Schleem","Skittlidoos","Dillywhopss"]}]